

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Unity Development
- C#
- Virtual Reality (VR)
- Augmented Reality (AR)
- Mixed Reality (MR)
- Unity 3D, 2D
- Game Development
- Easy AR
- AR Foundation
- Api

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

CONTACT

P: +02 01118996898 E: mohammref312@gmail.com W: www.linkedin.com/in/mohammref/

MOHAMED REFAAT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Software developer specializing in Unity, Virtual Reality, AR, and mobile games with production. I've been programming games for over five years on a variety of platforms. I have a solid understanding of programming fundamentals and design patterns in software. I also have a keen eye for other areas of design - be it related to UX, art, or gameplay logic. I am able to quickly create a well-structured, self-documenting code that is flexible and prepared for project evolutions. I've worked to tight deadlines on a raft of top budget productions for companies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EXTENDED REALITY DEVELOPER

IVY Stem International School | Nov 2022

- virtual Reality Applications
- Augmented reality Applications
- mixed reality Applications
- unity 3D development

EXTENDED REALITY DEVELOPER

bright Vision Company | Jan 2021 - Oct 2022

- virtual Reality Applications
- Augmented reality application
- unity 3D development

AUGMENTED REALITY FOR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSE

Mimic | Mar 2020 - Dec 2020

- augmented reality using EasyAR for educational
- unity 3D Applications

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF: COMPUTERS AND ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

University of Banha | 2015 - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Virtual Reality Nanodegree: Udacity. Introduction To Game Development: Coursera.

Programming Languages: C++, C# ,python.

REFERENCES

Portfolio of Work: Curated YouTube Playlist